{
  "cards": {
    "byIds": {
      "c-1" : {
          "id": "c-1",
          "front": "У нас нет хлеба",
          "back": "There is no bread here",
          "tags": [
            "there is"
          ],
          "lastRepeat": "2019-12-11T17:23:19.312Z",
          "status": "known"
        },
      "c-2": {
        "id": "c-2",
        "front": "На стене красивая картина",
        "back": "There is a beautiful painting on the wall",
        "tags": [
          "there is"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "2019-12-11T11:55:30.509Z",
        "status": "known"
      },
      "c-3": {
        "id": "c-3",
        "front": "В вазе были цветы",
        "back": "There were flowers in the vase",
        "tags": [
          "there is",
          "present past"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "2019-12-11T09:35:53.905Z",
        "status": "known"
      },
      "c-4": {
        "id": "c-4",
        "front": "Рыдая, она пошла обратно в дом",
        "back": "Weeping she walking back to the house",
        "tags": [
          "ing"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "2019-12-11T09:35:55.758Z",
        "status": "known"
      },
      "c-5": {
        "id": "c-5",
        "front": "Мне нравится вязание",
        "back": "I like knitting",
        "tags": [
          "ing"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "2019-12-11T09:35:57.932Z",
        "status": "known"
      },
      "c-6": {
        "id": "c-6",
        "front": "Ему приходится рано вставать",
        "back": "He has to get up early",
        "tags": [
          "modal verb"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "",
        "status": "repeat"
      },
      "c-7": {
        "id": "c-7",
        "front": "Я подумал, что её идея была просто потрясающей",
        "back": "I thought her new idea was absolutely fascinating",
        "tags": [
          "adverb"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "",
        "status": "repeat"
      },
      "c-8": {
        "id": "c-8",
        "front": "Все что-то делают",
        "back": "Everybody/everyone is doing something",
        "tags": [
          "pronouns"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "2019-12-11T17:23:19.312Z",
        "status": "repeat"
      },
      "c-9": {
        "id": "c-9",
        "front": "Никто никогда ничего не узнает",
        "back": "Nobody will ever find out anything",
        "tags": [
          "double negation"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "",
        "status": "repeat"
      },
      "c-10": {
        "id": "c-10",
        "front": "Она думала, что ее возьмут на работу",
        "back": "She thought she would get the job",
        "tags": [
          "sequence  of tenses"
        ],
        "lastRepeat": "",
        "status": "repeat"
      }
    },
    "allIds": ["c-1", "c-2", "c-3", "c-4", "c-5","c-6","c-7","c-8","c-9","c-10"]
  },
  "tests": {
    "q": {},
    "a": {}
  }
}